<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
    <ID>DATA CORRUPTED</ID>

    <Entry>
        <ID>jam_glitched_signal</ID>
        <Name>Unknown Signal</Name>

        <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
        <Curiosity>jam_glitched</Curiosity>

        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_signal_discovery</ID> 
            <Text>I detected a signal on an unknown frequency when I pointed my signalscope at a particular section of the sky. The signal contains Nomai text. I'm taking it to Hal to translate.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_signal_translation</ID> 
            <Text>The message carried by the signal describes a Nomai experiment in another solar system. Something about stabilizing stars!</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

    <Entry>
        <ID>jam_glitched_atp</ID>
        <Name>ATP Manipulation</Name>

        <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
        <Curiosity>jam_glitched</Curiosity>

        <RumorFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_atp_rumor</ID>
            <SourceID>jam_glitched_signal</SourceID>
            <Text></Text>
        </RumorFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_atp_discovery</ID> 
            <Text>I found some controls for the Ash Twin Project accessible using a Nomai staff. They contain options for the quantity of information sent back in time.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_atp_details</ID>
            <Text>By reducing the amount of information sent by the Ash Twin Project, I can increase the amount of time it is sent back by!</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

    <Entry>
        <ID>jam_glitched_plan</ID>
        <Name>A Plan</Name>

        <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
        <Curiosity>jam_glitched</Curiosity>

        <RumorFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_plan_rumor</ID>
            <SourceID>jam_glitched_atp</SourceID>
            <Text></Text>
        </RumorFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_plan_formulation</ID> 
            <Text>I have come up with a plan. I don't know how intact these logs will remain but I'm writing them anyways because if my plan succeeds, I will almost certainly forget what happened.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_glitched_plan_execution</ID>
            <Text>I'm going to set the Ash Twin Project to send as strong a signal as I can make as far back in time as possible, warning about the sun's explosion. In order to get that extra energy, I'm not going to be able to remember that last few loops. Hopefully Chert will pick up the signal and warn the others. Maybe they can evacuate to towards that Nomai signal I picked up. I hope...</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

    <Entry>
        <ID>jam_spark</ID>
        <Name>Clockwork Sun</Name>

        <Curiosity>jam_spark</Curiosity>
        <IsCuriosity/>

        <RumorFact>
            <ID>jam_spark_rumor</ID>
            <SourceID>jam_clocktower</SourceID>
            <RumorName>Solar Experiment</RumorName>
            <Text>A Nomai experiment involving this system's sun.</Text>
        </RumorFact>
        <ExploreFact>
            <ID>jam_spark_fact</ID> 
            <Text>There is a large clockwork Nomai structure at the core of the sun. There is a hole where a key would be inserted.</Text>
        </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>

</AstroObjectEntry>